Welcome to this section! I'm really excited
Bem vindo a esta seo! Estou muito animado para
for this section, because it is one of my passions.
esta seo, porque  uma das minhas paixes.
I have a number of other courses on this, and I think you're really going
Eu tenho uma srie de outros cursos sobre isso, e eu
to love learning about Flask and web development
acho que voc realmente vai adorar aprender sobre o Flask e
with Python.
desenvolvimento web com Python.
In this section
Nesta seo,
we're going to be giving users engaging
vamos oferecer aos usurios contedo envolvente,
content, getting data back from them,
receber dados deles e apresentar
and presenting everything in a nice, easy to use
tudo de uma forma agradvel e
fashion. Flask is excellent for that.
fcil de usar. O frasco  excelente para isso.
And Python is a really strong language for doing all
E Python  uma linguagem muito forte para fazer todo
sorts of web development as a whole.
tipo de desenvolvimento web como um todo.
Even from its use of decorators and database interactions,
Mesmo com o uso de decoradores e interaes de banco
all the way up to asynchronous development,
de dados, at o desenvolvimento assncrono, o Python  uma
Python is a great language to do this sort of stuff.
tima linguagem para fazer esse tipo de coisa.
With that said, I'll see you on the next video
Com isso dito, vejo vocs no prximo vdeo